do your nails with these forms prep your
nail and apply base coat
the form should fit sidewall to sidewall
applying gel perfect poly gel to the
form
dip your brush in slip solution and pat
it out
this is how it should look before i
place it on my nail
gently place that on your nail very
lightly push the form down
clean up product that was touching your
skin smoothing out the underside and
cuticle area
30 seconds in your lamp the form won't
move
so i'm adding more polygel to the
underside
place your full nail in the lamp squeeze
the sides of the form or use a tweezer
to remove
shape your nail and apply top coat and
you're done
gel perfect poly gel is so easy to work
with i love it